{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"9.0.1","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":4275,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":36,"width":1136,"height":640,"responsive":false,"scalable":true,"launchFile":"index_scorm.html"},"contentStructure":[{"id":"Text_Caption_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_2","title":"BRIDGE ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1","title":"BRIDGE ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_1","title":"Start ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5279","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Start ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5299","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Start ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_157","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_157","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_158","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_158","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_3","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_22","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_22","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide5126","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_2","Text_Caption_1","SmartShape_1","si5279","si5299","SmartShape_157","SmartShape_158","Image_3","Image_22"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5126"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_226","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_226","title":"Let’s see what you know!   This is a PRE-TEST!  It will not be graded.  Look at the sentences and choose the correct answer.   ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_156","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_156","title":"Numbers & Days of the Week ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_140","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_140","title":"Numbers & Days of the Week ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_141","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_141","title":"Take the Pre-Test ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16155","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Take the Pre-Test ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16175","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Take the Pre-Test ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide5385","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_226","SmartShape_156","SmartShape_140","SmartShape_141","si16155","si16175"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":135},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5385"}}},{"id":"si15568","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide5555q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5424","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_4","title":"Question 1 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5436","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_5","title":"What’s this number? \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t10 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5447","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_6","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5451","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_7","title":"One ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5447_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2","roles":{"answer":{"title":"One\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si5458","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_8","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5462","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_9","title":"Ten ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5458_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Ten\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si5545","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_1","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide5555q0","for":"Slide5555q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5500","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_3","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide5555q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5513","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_4","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide5555q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide5555","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si15568","si5424","si5436","si5451","si5462","si5545","si5500","si5513"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5555"},"question":{"interactionId":"5400","quizId":383,"title":"Question 1\r","text":"What’s this number?\r\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t10\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"]}}},{"id":"si16330","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16329q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16212","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_227","title":"Question 2 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16224","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_228","title":"What’s this number? \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t  7 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16235","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_229","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16239","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_230","title":"Six ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16235_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_72","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Six\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16246","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_231","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16250","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_232","title":"Seven ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16246_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_73","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Seven\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16319","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_44","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16329q1","for":"Slide16329q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16288","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_88","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16329q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16301","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_89","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16329q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16329","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si16330","si16212","si16224","si16239","si16250","si16319","si16288","si16301"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16329"},"question":{"interactionId":"16198","quizId":383,"title":"Question 2\r","text":"What’s this number?\r\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t  7\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"]}}},{"id":"si16491","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16490q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16373","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_233","title":"Question 3 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16385","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_234","title":"What’s this number? \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t    15 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16396","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_235","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16400","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_236","title":"Fifteen ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16396_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_74","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Fifteen\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16407","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_237","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16411","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_238","title":"Fifty ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16407_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_75","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Fifty\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16480","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_45","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16490q2","for":"Slide16490q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16449","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_90","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16490q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16462","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_91","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16490q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16490","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si16491","si16373","si16385","si16400","si16411","si16480","si16449","si16462"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16490"},"question":{"interactionId":"16359","quizId":383,"title":"Question 3\r","text":"What’s this number?\r\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t    15\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"]}}},{"id":"si16652","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16651q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16534","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_239","title":"Question 4 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16546","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_240","title":"What’s this number? \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t    22 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16557","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_241","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16561","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_242","title":"Twoty-Two ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16557_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_76","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Twoty-Two\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16568","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_243","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16572","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_244","title":"Twenty-Two ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16568_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_77","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Twenty-Two\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16641","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_46","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16651q3","for":"Slide16651q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16610","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_92","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16651q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16623","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_93","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16651q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16651","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si16652","si16534","si16546","si16561","si16572","si16641","si16610","si16623"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16651"},"question":{"interactionId":"16520","quizId":383,"title":"Question 4\r","text":"What’s this number?\r\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t    22\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"]}}},{"id":"si16813","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16812q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16695","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_245","title":"Question 5 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16707","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_246","title":"What’s this number? \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t \t   49 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16718","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_247","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16722","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_248","title":"Forty-Nine ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16718_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_78","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Forty-Nine\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16729","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_249","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16733","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_250","title":"Ninety-Four ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16729_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_79","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Ninety-Four\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16802","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_47","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16812q4","for":"Slide16812q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16771","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_99","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16812q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16784","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_101","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16812q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16812","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si16813","si16695","si16707","si16722","si16733","si16802","si16771","si16784"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16812"},"question":{"interactionId":"16681","quizId":383,"title":"Question 6\r","text":"What’s this number?\r\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t \t   49\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"]}}},{"id":"si16974","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16973q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16856","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_251","title":"Question 6 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16868","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_252","title":"What’s this number? \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t \t  100 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16879","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_253","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16883","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_254","title":"Tenty-Ten ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16879_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_80","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Tenty-Ten\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16890","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_255","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16894","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_256","title":"One-Hundred ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16890_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_81","roles":{"answer":{"title":"One-Hundred\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16963","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_48","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16973q5","for":"Slide16973q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16932","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_103","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16973q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16945","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_105","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide16973q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16973","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si16974","si16856","si16868","si16883","si16894","si16963","si16932","si16945"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16973"},"question":{"interactionId":"16842","quizId":383,"title":"Question 6\r","text":"What’s this number?\r\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t \t  100\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"]}}},{"id":"si17135","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide17134q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17017","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_257","title":"Question 7 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17029","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_258","title":"What’s the missing day?  \t\t\t1) Monday\t2) __________\t\t3) Wednesday ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17040","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_259","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17044","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_260","title":"Twosday ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17040_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_82","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Friday\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si17051","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_261","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17055","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_262","title":"Tuesday ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17051_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_83","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Freeday\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si17124","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_49","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17134q6","for":"Slide17134q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17093","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_107","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide17134q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17106","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_109","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide17134q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide17134","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si17135","si17017","si17029","si17044","si17055","si17124","si17093","si17106"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17134"},"question":{"interactionId":"17003","quizId":383,"title":"Question 7\r","text":"What’s the missing day?\r\r  \t 1) Wednesday \t2) Thursday\t3) __________\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"]}}},{"id":"si17296","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide17295q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17178","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_263","title":"Question 8 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17190","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_264","title":"What’s the missing day?    \t 1) Wednesday \t2) Thursday\t3) __________ ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17201","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_265","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17205","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_266","title":"Friday ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17201_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_84","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Friday\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si17212","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_267","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17216","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_268","title":"Freeday ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17212_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_85","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Freeday\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si17285","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_50","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17295q7","for":"Slide17295q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17254","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_111","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide17295q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17267","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_113","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide17295q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide17295","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si17296","si17178","si17190","si17205","si17216","si17285","si17254","si17267"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17295"},"question":{"interactionId":"17164","quizId":383,"title":"Question 8\r","text":"What’s the missing day?\r\r  \t 1) Wednesday \t2) Thursday\t3) __________\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"]}}},{"id":"si17457","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide17456q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17339","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_269","title":"Question 9 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17351","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_270","title":"What’s the missing day?    \t \t\t1) Friday\t\t2) Saturday  3) __________ ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17362","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_271","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17366","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_272","title":"Sunday ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17362_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_86","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Sunday\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si17373","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_273","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17377","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_274","title":"Funday ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17373_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_87","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Funday\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si17446","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_51","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17456q8","for":"Slide17456q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17415","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_131","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide17456q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17428","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_142","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide17456q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide17456","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si17457","si17339","si17351","si17366","si17377","si17446","si17415","si17428"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17456"},"question":{"interactionId":"17325","quizId":383,"title":"Question 9\r","text":"What’s the missing day?\r\r  \t \t\t1) Friday\t\t2) Saturday  3) __________\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"]}}},{"id":"si17618","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide17617q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17500","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_275","title":"Question 10 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17512","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_276","title":"What’s this number? \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t \t   0 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17523","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_277","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17527","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_278","title":"Ziro ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17523_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_88","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Ziro\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si17534","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_279","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17538","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_280","title":"Zero ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17534_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_89","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Zero\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si17607","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_52","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17617q9","for":"Slide17617q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17576","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_143","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide17617q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17589","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_144","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide17617q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide17617","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si17618","si17500","si17512","si17527","si17538","si17607","si17576","si17589"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17617"},"question":{"interactionId":"17486","quizId":383,"title":"Question 10\r","text":"What’s this number?\r\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t \t   0\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"]}}},{"id":"SmartShape_145","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_145","title":"Numbers 0-100 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_146","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_146","title":"Start ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17718","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Start ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17738","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Start ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_147","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_147","title":"Numbers 0-100 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide7103","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_145","SmartShape_146","si17718","si17738","SmartShape_147"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":183},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7103"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_24","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_24","title":"1 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7153","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"1 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7164","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"1 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_26","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_26","title":"2 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7235","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"2 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7246","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"2 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_27","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_27","title":"3 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7277","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"3 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7288","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"3 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_28","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_28","title":"4 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7319","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"4 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7330","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"4 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_29","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_29","title":"5 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7361","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"5 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7372","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"5 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_30","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_30","title":"6 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7403","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"6 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7414","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"6 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_31","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_31","title":"7 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7445","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"7 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7456","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"7 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_32","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_32","title":"8 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7487","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"8 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7498","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"8 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_33","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_33","title":"9 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7529","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"9 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7540","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"9 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_34","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_34","title":"0 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7571","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"0 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7582","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"0 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_64","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_64","title":"Click The Numbers & Repeat The Sound ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_65","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_65","title":"Ones ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_148","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_148","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17846","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17866","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide7606","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_24","si7153","si7164","SmartShape_26","si7235","si7246","SmartShape_27","si7277","si7288","SmartShape_28","si7319","si7330","SmartShape_29","si7361","si7372","SmartShape_30","si7403","si7414","SmartShape_31","si7445","si7456","SmartShape_32","si7487","si7498","SmartShape_33","si7529","si7540","SmartShape_34","si7571","si7582","Text_Caption_64","Text_Caption_65","SmartShape_148","si17846","si17866"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7606"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_37","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_37","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7782","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Click To Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7793","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Click To Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7805","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Click To Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_57","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_57","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_35","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_35","title":"Play ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7662","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Play ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7673","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Play ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7684","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_36","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_36","title":"1 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7732","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"1 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7743","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"1 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_38","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_38","title":"2 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7852","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"2 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7863","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"2 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_39","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_39","title":"3 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7910","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"3 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7921","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"3 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_40","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_40","title":"4 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7968","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"4 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7979","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"4 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_41","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_41","title":"5 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8026","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"5 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8037","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"5 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_42","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_42","title":"6 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8084","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"6 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8095","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"6 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_43","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_43","title":"7 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8142","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"7 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8153","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"7 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_44","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_44","title":"8 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8200","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"8 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8211","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"8 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_45","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_45","title":"9 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8258","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"9 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8269","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"9 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_46","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_46","title":"0 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8316","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"0 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8327","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"0 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_66","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_66","title":"Click The Correct Number ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"One_47","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"One_47","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8364","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"one ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8375","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Five_48","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Five_48","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8403","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Five ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8414","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"TWO_49","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"TWO_49","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8442","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Two ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8453","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SIX_50","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SIX_50","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8481","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Six ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8492","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"EIGHT_51","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"EIGHT_51","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8520","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"eight ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8531","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"THREE_52","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"THREE_52","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8559","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"three    ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8570","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"NINE_53","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"NINE_53","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8598","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Nine ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8609","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SEVEN_54","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SEVEN_54","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8637","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Seven   ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8648","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"FOUR_55","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"FOUR_55","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8676","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Four ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8687","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Ten_58","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Ten_58","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8769","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Zero   ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8780","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_56","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_56","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8714","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"CONGRATULATIONS! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8792","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_37","si7782","si7793","si7805","SmartShape_57","SmartShape_35","si7662","si7673","si7684","SmartShape_36","si7732","si7743","SmartShape_38","si7852","si7863","SmartShape_39","si7910","si7921","SmartShape_40","si7968","si7979","SmartShape_41","si8026","si8037","SmartShape_42","si8084","si8095","SmartShape_43","si8142","si8153","SmartShape_44","si8200","si8211","SmartShape_45","si8258","si8269","SmartShape_46","si8316","si8327","Text_Caption_66","One_47","si8364","si8375","Five_48","si8403","si8414","TWO_49","si8442","si8453","SIX_50","si8481","si8492","EIGHT_51","si8520","si8531","THREE_52","si8559","si8570","NINE_53","si8598","si8609","SEVEN_54","si8637","si8648","FOUR_55","si8676","si8687","Ten_58","si8769","si8780","SmartShape_56","si8714"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":300},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8792"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_59","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_59","title":"10 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8842","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"10 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8853","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"10 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_61","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_61","title":"20 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8924","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"20 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8935","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"20 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_62","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_62","title":"30 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8966","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"30 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8977","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"30 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_63","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_63","title":"40 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9008","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"40 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9019","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"40 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_64","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_64","title":"50 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9050","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"50 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9061","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"50 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_65","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_65","title":"60 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9092","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"60 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9103","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"60 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_66","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_66","title":"70 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9134","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"70 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9145","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"70 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_67","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_67","title":"80 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9176","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"80 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9187","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"80 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_68","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_68","title":"90 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9218","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"90 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9229","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"90 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_69","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_69","title":"100 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9260","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"100 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9271","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"100 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_67","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_67","title":"Click The Numbers & Repeat The Sound ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_68","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_68","title":"Tens ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_149","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_149","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18182","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18202","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide9295","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_59","si8842","si8853","SmartShape_61","si8924","si8935","SmartShape_62","si8966","si8977","SmartShape_63","si9008","si9019","SmartShape_64","si9050","si9061","SmartShape_65","si9092","si9103","SmartShape_66","si9134","si9145","SmartShape_67","si9176","si9187","SmartShape_68","si9218","si9229","SmartShape_69","si9260","si9271","Text_Caption_67","Text_Caption_68","SmartShape_149","si18182","si18202"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9295"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_70","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_70","title":"Play ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9351","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Play ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9362","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Play ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9373","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_71","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_71","title":"10 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9421","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"10 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9432","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"10 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_72","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_72","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9471","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Click To Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9482","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Click To Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9494","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Click To Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_73","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_73","title":"20 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9541","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"20 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9552","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"20 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_74","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_74","title":"30 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9599","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"30 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9610","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"30 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_75","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_75","title":"40 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9657","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"40 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9668","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"40 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_76","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_76","title":"50 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9715","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"50 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9726","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"50 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_77","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_77","title":"60 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9773","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"60 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9784","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"60 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_78","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_78","title":"70 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9831","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"70 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9842","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"70 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_79","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_79","title":"80 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9889","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"80 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9900","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"80 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_80","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_80","title":"90 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9947","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"90 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9958","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"90 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_81","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_81","title":"100 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10005","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"100 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10016","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"100 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_69","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_69","title":"Click The Correct Number ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_82","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_82","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10052","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"CONGRATULATIONS! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_83","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_83","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hundred_84","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hundred_84","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10107","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"one  hundred    ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10118","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"FOURTY_85","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"FOURTY_85","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10146","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"fourty      ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10157","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SEVENTY_86","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SEVENTY_86","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10185","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"seventy     ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10196","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"NINETY_87","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"NINETY_87","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10224","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"ninety     ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10235","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"THIRTY_88","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"THIRTY_88","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10263","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"thirty    ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10274","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"EIGHTY_89","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"EIGHTY_89","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10302","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"eighty    ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10313","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SIXTY_90","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SIXTY_90","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10341","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"sixty   ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10352","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"TWENTY_91","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"TWENTY_91","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10380","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"twenty            ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10391","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Fifty_92","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Fifty_92","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10419","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"fifty ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10430","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Tenty_93","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Tenty_93","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10458","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"ten ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10469","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide10481","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_70","si9351","si9362","si9373","SmartShape_71","si9421","si9432","SmartShape_72","si9471","si9482","si9494","SmartShape_73","si9541","si9552","SmartShape_74","si9599","si9610","SmartShape_75","si9657","si9668","SmartShape_76","si9715","si9726","SmartShape_77","si9773","si9784","SmartShape_78","si9831","si9842","SmartShape_79","si9889","si9900","SmartShape_80","si9947","si9958","SmartShape_81","si10005","si10016","Text_Caption_69","SmartShape_82","si10052","SmartShape_83","Hundred_84","si10107","si10118","FOURTY_85","si10146","si10157","SEVENTY_86","si10185","si10196","NINETY_87","si10224","si10235","THIRTY_88","si10263","si10274","EIGHTY_89","si10302","si10313","SIXTY_90","si10341","si10352","TWENTY_91","si10380","si10391","Fifty_92","si10419","si10430","Tenty_93","si10458","si10469"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":300},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide10481"}}},{"id":"si15678","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10659q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_70","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_70","title":"21 = 20 + 1 \t\tTwenty-one\t\t\t49 = 40 + 9 \tForty-nine  33 = 30 + 3 \tThirty-three\t\t\t52 = 50 + 2\t\tFifty-two 68 = 60 + 8\t\tSixty-eight\t\t\t84 = 80 + 4 \tEighty-four ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_71","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_71","title":"What’s this number: 76 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_11","roles":{}},{"id":"si10528","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_72","title":"Filling In The Gaps ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10540","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_73","title":"To make the other numbers, add the tens and ones ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10551","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_74","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10555","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_75","title":"Seven-six ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10551_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"35","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Seven-six\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10562","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_76","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10566","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_77","title":"Seventy-six ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10562_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"37","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Seventy-six\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10649","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_11","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide10659q10","for":"Slide10659q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10604","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_47","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10659q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10617","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_48","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10659q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide10659","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si15678","Text_Caption_70","Text_Caption_71","Image_11","si10528","si10540","si10555","si10566","si10649","si10604","si10617"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide10659"},"question":{"interactionId":"10496","quizId":383,"title":"Tens & Ones\r","text":"To make the other numbers, add the tens and ones\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"]}}},{"id":"SmartShape_150","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_150","title":"Matching ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_151","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_151","title":"Start ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18305","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Start ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18316","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Start ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_152","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_152","title":"Matching ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide18342","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_150","SmartShape_151","si18305","si18316","SmartShape_152"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":183},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide18342"}}},{"id":"si15860","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide11112q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10822","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_78","title":"Select from the drop down menu or  drag & drop the numbers to their spellings  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_79","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_79","title":"B ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_80","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_80","title":"15 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_81","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_81","title":"E ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_82","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_82","title":"99 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_83","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_83","title":"H ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_84","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_84","title":"31 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_85","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_85","title":"G ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_86","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_86","title":"27 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_87","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_87","title":"A ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_88","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_88","title":"43 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_89","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_89","title":"C ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_90","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_90","title":"2 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_91","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_91","title":"D ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_92","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_92","title":"50 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_93","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_93","title":"F ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_94","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_94","title":"86 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10922","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_95","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10926","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_96","title":"Forty-three ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10926ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Forty-three","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si10932","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_97","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10936","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_98","title":"Fifteen ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10936ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Fifteen","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si10942","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_99","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10946","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_100","title":"Two ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10946ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Two","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si10952","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_101","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10956","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_102","title":"Fifty ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10956ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Fifty","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si10962","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_103","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10966","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_104","title":"Ninety-nine ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10966ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Ninety-nine","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si10972","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_105","title":"F) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10976","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_106","title":"Eighty-six ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10976ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Eighty-six","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si10982","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_107","title":"G) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10986","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_108","title":"Twenty-seven ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10986ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Twenty-seven","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si10992","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_109","title":"H) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10996","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_110","title":"Thirty-one ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10996ans","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Thirty-one","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si11071","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_12","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide11112q11","for":"Slide11112q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11088","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_111","title":"Number Matching  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15873","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_224","title":"Numbers ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15882","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_225","title":"Spelling  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11039","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_49","title":"Try again ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide11112q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11102","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_50","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide11112q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide11112","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si15860","si10822","si10926","si10936","si10946","si10956","si10966","si10976","si10986","si10996","si11071","si11088","si11039","si11102"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide11112"},"question":{"interactionId":"10751","quizId":383,"title":"Number Matching\r\r","text":"Select from the drop down menu or \rdrag & drop the numbers to their spellings \r","type":"knowledgeCheck","ikc":true,"interactionType":"matching","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":[]}}},{"id":"SmartShape_162","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_162","title":"Days of the Week ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_163","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_163","title":"Start ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18767","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Start ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18778","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Start ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_164","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_164","title":"Days of the Week ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide18804","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_162","SmartShape_163","si18767","si18778","SmartShape_164"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":183},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide18804"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_98","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_98","title":"Sunday ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11475","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Sunday ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11486","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Sunday ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"sunday_99","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"sunday_99","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11521","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"[SUHN-dey] ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_100","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_100","title":"Monday ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11570","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Monday ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11581","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Monday ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"monday_101","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"monday_101","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11608","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"[MUHN-dey] ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_102","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_102","title":"Tuesday ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11657","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Tuesday ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11668","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Tuesday ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"tuesday_103","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"tuesday_103","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11695","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"[TOOZ-dey] ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_104","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_104","title":"Wednesday ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11744","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Wednesday ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11755","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Wednesday ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"wednesday_105","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"wednesday_105","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11782","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"[WENZ-dey] ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_106","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_106","title":"Thursday ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11831","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Thursday ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11842","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Thursday ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"thursday_107","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"thursday_107","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11869","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"[THURZ-dey] ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_108","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_108","title":"Friday ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11918","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Friday ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11929","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Friday ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"friday_109","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"friday_109","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11956","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"[FRAHY-dey] ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_110","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_110","title":"Saturday ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12005","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Saturday ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12016","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Saturday ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"saturday_111","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"saturday_111","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12043","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"[SAT-er-dey] ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_112","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_112","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12072","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12083","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"block_113","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"block_113","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_112","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_112","title":"Click and Repeat the Sound ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12122","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_98","si11475","si11486","sunday_99","si11521","SmartShape_100","si11570","si11581","monday_101","si11608","SmartShape_102","si11657","si11668","tuesday_103","si11695","SmartShape_104","si11744","si11755","wednesday_105","si11782","SmartShape_106","si11831","si11842","thursday_107","si11869","SmartShape_108","si11918","si11929","friday_109","si11956","SmartShape_110","si12005","si12016","saturday_111","si12043","SmartShape_112","si12072","si12083","block_113","Text_Caption_112"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":93},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12122"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_121","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_121","title":"Drag & Drop the Days of the Week into the Correct Order ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_114","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_114","title":"Sunday ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_115","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_115","title":"Monday ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_116","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_116","title":"Tuesday ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_117","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_117","title":"Wednesday ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_118","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_118","title":"Thursday ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_119","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_119","title":"Friday ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_120","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_120","title":"Saturday ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_121","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_121","title":"Day 1 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_122","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_122","title":"Day 2 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_123","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_123","title":"Day 3 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_124","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_124","title":"Day 4 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_125","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_125","title":"Day 5 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_126","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_126","title":"Day 6 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_127","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_127","title":"Day 7 ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_2","title":"CORRECT ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_17","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_17","roles":{}},{"id":"Button_18","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_18","roles":{}},{"id":"Button_19","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_19","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide12996","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_121","SmartShape_114","SmartShape_115","SmartShape_116","SmartShape_117","SmartShape_118","SmartShape_119","SmartShape_120","SmartShape_121","SmartShape_122","SmartShape_123","SmartShape_124","SmartShape_125","SmartShape_126","SmartShape_127","Success_Shape_2"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":132},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12996"},"dragDrop":{"sources":[12485,12534,12574,12614,12654,12694,12734],"targets":[12751,12768,12785,12802,12819,12836,12853]}}},{"id":"SmartShape_178","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_178","title":"Take The Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_179","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_179","title":"Start ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19877","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Start ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19888","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Start ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_180","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_180","title":"Take The Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide19914","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_178","SmartShape_179","si19877","si19888","SmartShape_180"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":183},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide19914"}}},{"id":"si15700","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13964q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13790","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_128","title":"Question 1 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13802","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_129","title":"Today is Wednesday. Tomorrow is _________. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13813","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_130","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13817","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_131","title":"Twoozday ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13813_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"130_40","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Twoozday\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si13824","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_132","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13828","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_133","title":"Thursday ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13824_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"132_41","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Thursday\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si13835","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_134","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13839","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_135","title":"Thirsday ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13835_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"134_42","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Thirsday\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si13846","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_136","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13850","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_137","title":"Thirdsday ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13846_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"136_43","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Thirdsday\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si13920","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_20","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide13964q12","for":"Slide13964q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13940","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_21","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide13964q12","for":"Slide13964q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13954","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_22","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide13964q12","for":"Slide13964q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13888","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_53","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13964q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide13964","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si15700","si13790","si13802","si13817","si13828","si13839","si13850","si13920","si13940","si13954","si13888"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide13964"},"question":{"interactionId":"13770","quizId":383,"title":"Question 1\r","text":"Today is Wednesday. Tomorrow is _________.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si20520","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide20519q13"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20357","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_281","title":"Question 2 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20369","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_282","title":"What number is this?   \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t22 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20380","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_283","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20384","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_284","title":"Two-two ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20380_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"130_90","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Two-two\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si20391","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_285","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20395","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_286","title":"Twinty-two ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20391_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"132_91","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Twinty-two\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si20405","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_287","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20409","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_288","title":"Twenty-two ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20405_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"134_92","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Twenty-two\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si20416","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_289","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20420","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_290","title":"Twoty-two ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20416_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"136_93","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Twoty-two\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si20464","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_53","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide20519q13","for":"Slide20519q13"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20484","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_54","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide20519q13","for":"Slide20519q13"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20498","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_55","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide20519q13","for":"Slide20519q13"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20446","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_159","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide20519q13"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide20519","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si20520","si20357","si20369","si20384","si20395","si20409","si20420","si20464","si20484","si20498","si20446"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide20519"},"question":{"interactionId":"20343","quizId":383,"title":"Question 2\r","text":"What number is this? \r\r\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t22\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si20734","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide20733q14"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20571","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_293","title":"Question 3 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20583","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_294","title":"What number is this?   \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t15 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20594","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_295","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20598","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_296","title":"Fifty ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20594_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"130_94","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Fifty\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si20605","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_297","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20609","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_298","title":"Fiftin ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20605_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"132_95","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Fiftin\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si20619","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_299","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20623","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_300","title":"Fifteen ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20619_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"134_96","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Fifteen\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si20630","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_301","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20634","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_302","title":"Fiveteen ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20630_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"136_97","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Fiveteen\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si20678","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_56","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide20733q14","for":"Slide20733q14"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20698","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_57","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide20733q14","for":"Slide20733q14"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20712","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_58","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide20733q14","for":"Slide20733q14"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20660","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_160","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide20733q14"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide20733","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si20734","si20571","si20583","si20598","si20609","si20623","si20634","si20678","si20698","si20712","si20660"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide20733"},"question":{"interactionId":"20557","quizId":383,"title":"Question 3\r","text":"What number is this? \r\r\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t15\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si20953","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide20952q15"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20790","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_305","title":"Question 4 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20802","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_306","title":"What’s the next day?  \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t1. Wednesday \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t2. Thursday \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t3. __________ \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t15 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20813","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_307","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20817","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_308","title":"Fridai ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20813_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"130_98","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Fridai\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si20824","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_309","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20828","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_310","title":"Freeday ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20824_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"132_99","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Freeday\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si20838","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_311","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20842","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_312","title":"Fryday ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20838_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"134_100","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Fryday\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si20849","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_313","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20853","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_314","title":"Friday ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20849_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"136_101","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Friday\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si20897","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_59","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide20952q15","for":"Slide20952q15"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20917","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_60","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide20952q15","for":"Slide20952q15"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20931","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_61","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide20952q15","for":"Slide20952q15"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20879","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_161","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide20952q15"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide20952","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si20953","si20790","si20802","si20817","si20828","si20842","si20853","si20897","si20917","si20931","si20879"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide20952"},"question":{"interactionId":"20776","quizId":383,"title":"Question 4\r","text":"What’s the next day?\r\r\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t1. Wednesday\r\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t2. Thursday\r\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t3. __________\r\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t15\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si21167","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide21166q16"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21004","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_317","title":"Question 5 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21016","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_318","title":"What’s the next day?  \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t1. Saturday \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t2. Sunday \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t3. __________ \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t15 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21027","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_319","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21031","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_320","title":"Munday ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21027_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"130_102","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Munday\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21038","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_321","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21042","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_322","title":"Manday ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21038_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"132_103","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Manday\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21052","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_323","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21056","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_324","title":"Moonday ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21052_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"134_104","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Moonday\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21063","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_325","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21067","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_326","title":"Monday ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21063_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"136_105","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Monday\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si21111","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_62","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide21166q16","for":"Slide21166q16"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21131","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_63","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide21166q16","for":"Slide21166q16"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21145","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_64","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide21166q16","for":"Slide21166q16"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21093","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_165","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide21166q16"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide21166","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si21167","si21004","si21016","si21031","si21042","si21056","si21067","si21111","si21131","si21145","si21093"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide21166"},"question":{"interactionId":"20990","quizId":383,"title":"Question 5\r","text":"What’s the next day?\r\r\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t1. Saturday\r\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t2. Sunday\r\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t3. __________\r\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t15\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si21381","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide21380q17"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21218","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_329","title":"Question 6 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21230","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_330","title":"What number is this?   \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t79 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21241","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_331","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21245","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_332","title":"Seventy-nine ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21241_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"130_106","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Seventy-nine\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si21252","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_333","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21256","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_334","title":"Seven-nine ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21252_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"132_107","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Seven-nine\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21266","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_335","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21270","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_336","title":"Ninety-seven ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21266_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"134_108","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Ninety-seven\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21277","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_337","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21281","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_338","title":"Seven-ninety ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21277_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"136_109","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Seven-ninety\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21325","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_65","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide21380q17","for":"Slide21380q17"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21345","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_66","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide21380q17","for":"Slide21380q17"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21359","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_67","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide21380q17","for":"Slide21380q17"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21307","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_166","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide21380q17"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide21380","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si21381","si21218","si21230","si21245","si21256","si21270","si21281","si21325","si21345","si21359","si21307"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide21380"},"question":{"interactionId":"21204","quizId":383,"title":"Question 6\r","text":"What number is this? \r\r\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t79\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si21595","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide21594q18"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21432","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_341","title":"Question 7 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21444","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_342","title":"What number is this?   \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t100 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21455","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_343","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21459","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_344","title":"Tenty-ten ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21455_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"130_110","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Tenty-ten\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21466","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_345","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21470","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_346","title":"One-zero-zero ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21466_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"132_111","roles":{"answer":{"title":"One-zero-zero\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21480","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_347","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21484","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_348","title":"One-hundred ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21480_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"134_112","roles":{"answer":{"title":"One-hundred\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si21491","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_349","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21495","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_350","title":"Onety-ten ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21491_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"136_113","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Onety-ten\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21539","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_68","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide21594q18","for":"Slide21594q18"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21559","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_69","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide21594q18","for":"Slide21594q18"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21573","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_70","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide21594q18","for":"Slide21594q18"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21521","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_167","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide21594q18"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide21594","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si21595","si21432","si21444","si21459","si21470","si21484","si21495","si21539","si21559","si21573","si21521"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide21594"},"question":{"interactionId":"21418","quizId":383,"title":"Question 7\r","text":"What number is this? \r\r\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t100\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si21809","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide21808q19"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21646","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_353","title":"Question 8 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21658","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_354","title":"What are the days of the weekend? \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21669","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_355","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21673","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_356","title":"Friday and Saturday ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21669_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"130_114","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Friday and Saturday\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21680","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_357","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21684","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_358","title":"Saturday and Sunday ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21680_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"132_115","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Saturday and Sunday\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si21694","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_359","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21698","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_360","title":"Thursday and Friday ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21694_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"134_116","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Thursday and Friday\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21705","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_361","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21709","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_362","title":"Sunday and Monday ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21705_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"136_117","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Sunday and Monday\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21753","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_71","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide21808q19","for":"Slide21808q19"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21773","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_72","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide21808q19","for":"Slide21808q19"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21787","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_73","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide21808q19","for":"Slide21808q19"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21735","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_168","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide21808q19"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide21808","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si21809","si21646","si21658","si21673","si21684","si21698","si21709","si21753","si21773","si21787","si21735"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide21808"},"question":{"interactionId":"21632","quizId":383,"title":"Question 8\r","text":"What are the days of the weekend?\r\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si22237","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide22236q20"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22074","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_377","title":"Question 9 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22086","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_378","title":"What number is this?   \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t99 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22097","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_379","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22101","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_380","title":"Ninety-ninety ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22097_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"130_122","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Ninety-ninety\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22108","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_381","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22112","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_382","title":"Nine-nine ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22108_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"132_123","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Nine-nine\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22122","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_383","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22126","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_384","title":"Ninety-nine ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22122_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"134_124","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Ninety-nine\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si22133","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_385","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22137","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_386","title":"Nine-ninety ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22133_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"136_125","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Nine-ninety\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22181","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_77","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22236q20","for":"Slide22236q20"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22201","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_78","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22236q20","for":"Slide22236q20"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22215","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_79","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22236q20","for":"Slide22236q20"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22163","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_170","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide22236q20"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide22236","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si22237","si22074","si22086","si22101","si22112","si22126","si22137","si22181","si22201","si22215","si22163"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide22236"},"question":{"interactionId":"22060","quizId":383,"title":"Question 9\r","text":"What number is this? \r\r\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t99\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si22023","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide22022q21"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21860","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_365","title":"Question 10 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21872","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_366","title":"What number is this?   \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t84 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21883","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_367","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21887","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_368","title":"Eighty-forty ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21883_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"130_118","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Eighty-forty\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21894","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_369","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21898","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_370","title":"Forty-eight ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21894_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"132_119","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Forty-eight\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21908","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_371","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21912","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_372","title":"Eighty-eight ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21908_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"134_120","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Eighty-eight\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21919","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_373","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21923","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_374","title":"Eighty-four ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21919_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"136_121","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Eighty-four\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si21967","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_74","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22022q21","for":"Slide22022q21"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21987","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_75","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22022q21","for":"Slide22022q21"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22001","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_76","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22022q21","for":"Slide22022q21"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21949","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_169","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide22022q21"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide22022","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si22023","si21860","si21872","si21887","si21898","si21912","si21923","si21967","si21987","si22001","si21949"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide22022"},"question":{"interactionId":"21846","quizId":383,"title":"Question 10\r","text":"What number is this? \r\r\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t84\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_184","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_184","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15921","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si22288","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si15910","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Quiz Results ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15917","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You Scored: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15969","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22284","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Accuracy: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22292","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide15889","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide15889"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_181","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_181","title":"End of Section  Numbers & Days ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_182","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_182","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19998","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20009","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_183","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_183","title":"End of Section Numbers & Days ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide20035","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_181","SmartShape_182","si19998","si20009","SmartShape_183"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":183},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide20035"}}},{"id":"Pool427","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":427,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"NumbersDays","class":"project","title":"NumbersDays","children":["Slide5126","Slide5385","Slide5555","Slide16329","Slide16490","Slide16651","Slide16812","Slide16973","Slide17134","Slide17295","Slide17456","Slide17617","Slide7103","Slide7606","Slide8792","Slide9295","Slide10481","Slide10659","Slide18342","Slide11112","Slide18804","Slide12122","Slide12996","Slide19914","Slide13964","Slide20519","Slide20733","Slide20952","Slide21166","Slide21380","Slide21594","Slide21808","Slide22236","Slide22022","Slide15889","Slide20035"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":383,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide5555q0","Slide16329q1","Slide16490q2","Slide16651q3","Slide16812q4","Slide16973q5","Slide17134q6","Slide17295q7","Slide17456q8","Slide17617q9","Slide10659q10","Slide11112q11","Slide13964q12","Slide20519q13","Slide20733q14","Slide20952q15","Slide21166q16","Slide21380q17","Slide21594q18","Slide21808q19","Slide22236q20","Slide22022q21"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":10,"passScore":8}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide5126","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide5385","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide5555","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide16329","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide16490","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide16651","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide16812","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide16973","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide17134","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide17295","title":"Slide 10"},{"id":"Slide17456","title":"Slide 11"},{"id":"Slide17617","title":"Slide 12"},{"id":"Slide7103","title":"Slide 13"},{"id":"Slide7606","title":"Slide 14"},{"id":"Slide8792","title":"Slide 15"},{"id":"Slide9295","title":"Slide 16"},{"id":"Slide10481","title":"Slide 17"},{"id":"Slide10659","title":"Slide 18"},{"id":"Slide18342","title":"Slide 19"},{"id":"Slide11112","title":"Slide 20"},{"id":"Slide18804","title":"Slide 21"},{"id":"Slide12122","title":"Slide 22"},{"id":"Slide12996","title":"Slide 23"},{"id":"Slide19914","title":"Slide 24"},{"id":"Slide13964","title":"Slide 25"},{"id":"Slide20519","title":"Slide 26"},{"id":"Slide20733","title":"Slide 27"},{"id":"Slide20952","title":"Slide 28"},{"id":"Slide21166","title":"Slide 29"},{"id":"Slide21380","title":"Slide 30"},{"id":"Slide21594","title":"Slide 31"},{"id":"Slide21808","title":"Slide 32"},{"id":"Slide22236","title":"Slide 33"},{"id":"Slide22022","title":"Slide 34"},{"id":"Slide15889","title":"Slide 35"},{"id":"Slide20035","title":"Slide 36"}]}